{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866464069","data":{"timestamp":" 946866464069"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" b1eb2d20-3118-43d1-bf15-8b14403d8356"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.100..900.GL_DD_OFF100_L.bub3.34"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_871_871-971-1071"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866501073","data":{"timestamp":" 946866501073"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_117v392"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 392"," userResponse":" 392"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866507884","data":{"timestamp":" 946866507883"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_485v255"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 485"," userResponse":" 485"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866540555","data":{"timestamp":" 946866540555"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_477v210"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 477"," userResponse":" 210"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866553439","data":{"timestamp":" 946866553439"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_477v210"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 477"," userResponse":" 477"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866554151","data":{"timestamp":" 946866554151"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_477v210"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 477"," userResponse":" 477"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866558516","data":{"timestamp":" 946866558516"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_289v112"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 289"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866560418","data":{"timestamp":" 946866560418"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_289v112"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 289"," userResponse":" 112"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866564147","data":{"timestamp":" 946866564146"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_289v112"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 289"," userResponse":" 289"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866578057","data":{"timestamp":" 946866578057"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_219v275"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 275"," userResponse":" 275"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866579247","data":{"timestamp":" 946866579247"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_219v275"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 275"," userResponse":" 219"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866581186","data":{"timestamp":" 946866581186"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 229"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866582493","data":{"timestamp":" 946866582493"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 229"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866583953","data":{"timestamp":" 946866583952"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 229"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866585718","data":{"timestamp":" 946866585718"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 311"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866588062","data":{"timestamp":" 946866588062"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 311"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866588233","data":{"timestamp":" 946866588232"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 311"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866588615","data":{"timestamp":" 946866588615"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_229v311"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 311"," userResponse":" 311"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866593371","data":{"timestamp":" 946866593370"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_203v116"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 203"," userResponse":" 116"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866595277","data":{"timestamp":" 946866595277"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_203v116"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 203"," userResponse":" 203"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:3d.compare.random","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866599953","data":{"timestamp":" 946866599953"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_203v116"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866606432","data":{"timestamp":" 946866606432"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000103_052735"," gameId":" 1a9a66ca-f1e2-48df-8bed-a9ab11f42307"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_3d.compare.random"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_203v116"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}